asseenontv.com 2010-12-30

# AsSeenOnTV.com - The Official Site for As Seen On TV - Best Prices! - Order Now! 866-277-3366

**About AsSeenOnTV.com™ and SeenOnTV.com®**  
---  
| 

**Privacy and Security Policy**

At AsSeenOnTV.com and SeeOnTV.com (collectively, "AsSeenOnTV"), we recognize that privacy is an important issue for persons who disclose personal information. As such, we have developed this Privacy and Security Policy (the "Privacy Policy") which applies to all of the products, services and the websites offered by AsSeenOnTV or its subsidiaries or affiliated companies (collectively, the AsSeenOnTV "Services"). This Privacy Policy discloses the information gathering, use and dissemination practices of AsSeenOnTV with respect to personal information (collectively, "User Data") provided by users of our websites (each a "User"), including without limitation persons who access the AsSeenOnTV websites, purchase a product or service, enroll in a program, or register a promotion or special offer at the AsSeenOnTV websites. Each User acknowledges and understands that AsSeenOnTV may change this Privacy Policy by posting a new Version on the websites the terms and conditions of which will be binding on each User. By submitting your User Data to AsSeenOnTV, you are agreeing to the terms of the this Privacy Policy, as it may amended from time to time.   
  
---  
  
* * *  
  
**What information do we collect from you and how do we use it?**  
  
**•  Personal Information You Provide** � We may collect information necessary to contact you later. If we collect personal information (as described below), you may later access and modify it, and remove it from our system. You may also choose simply not to provide your personal information at the point of collection. When you enter your personal information on the AsSeenOnTV websites, you are providing User Data. User Data may include first name, last name, a home or other physical mailing address, a telephone number, or other "real world" contact information, plus other information voluntarily selected by a User that is collected from the User and is maintained in personally identifiable form in combination with an identifier described above. User Data may be collected on the main registration page as well as any subsequent pages. For certain Services, AsSeenOnTV may give you the opportunity to opt out of providing any such information.  
  
**•  IP Addresses ** \- AsSeenOnTV uses your Internet Protocol (IP) address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our websites. IP addresses are recorded so that we can offer the best possible customer service to you at all times.  
  
**•  Personal Email Address ** \- We may request your email address, or other information needed to contact you online. AsSeenOnTV uses your email address to complete, support and analyze your purchases from the AsSeenOnTV websites and use of the AsSeenOnTV websites, and to comply with any applicable laws, rules and regulations. We use it to respond to any questions you might have and to provide you with information about promotions or special offers occurring on the AsSeenOnTV websites if you have chosen to participate in this Service. This information may be disclosed to our staff and to third parties involved in the completion of your transaction, the delivery of your order or the analysis and support of your use of the AsSeenOnTV websites.  
  
**•  Cookies ** \- When you visit the AsSeenOnTV websites, we send one or more cookies (a small file containing a string of characters) to your personal computer that uniquely identifies your browser. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service by storing user preferences and tracking user trends, such as how people search. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some AsSeenOnTV features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled.   
  
**•  Log information ** \- When you use AsSeenOnTV services, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, IP address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.   
  
**•  User communications ** \- When you send email or other communication to AsSeenOnTV, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services.   
  
**•  Affiliated sites ** \- We offer some of our Services in connection with other web sites. Personal information that you provide to those sites may be sent to an affiliated site (including third party marketing partners or advertising companies) in order to deliver the Service.   
  
**•  Links ** \- AsSeenOnTV may present links in a format that enables us to keep track of whether these links have been followed. We use this information to improve the quality of our search technology, customized content and advertising.   
  
**•  Other sites ** \- This Privacy Policy applies to websites and Services that are owned and operated by AsSeenOnTV. We do not exercise control over the sites displayed as search results or links from within our various services. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you.  
  
**•  Clickstream Data ** \- As you browse our the AsSeenOnTV websites, we may gather navigational and clickstream data that shows what pages are visited and how long various features are used. This information will not reveal your identity or be linked to you personally. We use this information to complete, analyze and support your purchases from the AsSeenOnTv websites and use of the AsSeenOnTv websites to comply with any requirements of law and to determine the commissions for our affiliates.  
  
**•  Promotions and Sweepstakes Registration Information ** \- By entering a sweepstakes or other promotions on the AsSeenOnTV websites, you are agreeing to provide registration information to AsSeenOnTV. As condition to eligibility for the promotions and sweepstakes, each User acknowledges and hereby authorizes AsSeenOnTV to sell, distribute or share such information with any third party marketing partners on the subsequent data survey pages, promotions and sweepstakes confirmation pages or in later email offers delivered on the AsSeenOnTV websites. All User Data that is submitted in connection with a product or service purchase or with a program or promotion enrollment shall become the property of AsSeenOnTV and may be used by AsSeenOnTV in the future for marketing or other purposes. If you take advantage of marketing opportunities offered by one or more of AsSeenOnTV third party marketing partners, your User Data will also become the property of such third party marketing partner and we recommend that you review each of the marketing partners' privacy policies to understand how they treat such information.  
  
**•  Other Information ** � In addition to the other information described above, we may collect information actively generated by the purchase of a product or service, such as a payment method. The AsSeenOnTV websites use an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitor's contact information (email address) and financial information (account). Contact information from the order form is used to send orders to our customers. We use this information to process your order and analyze and support your use of the AsSeenOnTV websites. For certain Services, we may also request credit card or other payment account information which we maintain in encrypted form on secure servers. We may combine the information you submit under your account with information from other AsSeenOnTV Services or third parties in order to provide you with a better experience and to improve the quality of our Services.   
  
* * *  
  
**Additional Uses of Information**

We use the collected information described above to complete, support and analyze your purchases from the AsSeenOnTV websites, use of the AsSeenOnTV websites, for other internal purposes and to comply with any requirements of all applicable laws, rules and regulations. In addition, this information may be disclosed to our staff and to third parties involved in the completion of your transaction, the delivery of your order or the analysis and support of your use of the AsSeenOnTV websites. Certain information (excluding credit card account) will also be sold, exchanged or otherwise disclosed to third parties, at the discretion of AsSeenOnTV, including without limitation third party marketing firms and third party affiliates to be used for direct target marketing to you (via mail, email or otherwise). You hereby authorize AsSeenOnTV to sell, exchange or distribute all or a portion of your personal information with or to third parties for their use in direct target marketing to you.

You acknowledge and agree that your personal information may be used and reproduced for any legitimate business purpose including the training of our customer service representatives. In addition, we may use any ideas, concepts or techniques contained in such information for any purpose, including developing, improving or marketing our products and services. This Privacy Policy applies solely to the AsSeenOnTV websites and our on-line activities directly and indirectly relating to it. If the AsSeenOnTV websites is linked to, or from, a website of another entity or company, we are not responsible for the privacy, practices or policy of the other entity in any way, or the content of its website. You may later access and modify any of your personal information, or have it removed from the AsSeenOnTV websites. You may also simply choose not to provide your personal information at the point of collection; however, if you do not provide such information, we will be unable to complete your purchase.   
  
* * *  
  
**Choice/Opt-Out**

As mentioned above, the AsSeenOnTV websites allows each User the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us. The websites allow Users to remove themselves from our distribution list to cease receiving future communications and to no longer receive our Services. If you would like to opt out at any time from receiving e-mail messages and other communications from the AsSeenOnTV websites, please contact us at [unsubscribe@AsSeenOnTV.com](mailto:unsubscribe@AsSeenOnTV.com) or at the address below. 

You acknowledge and agree that, once any of your information is disclosed or sold to any third party, AsSeenOnTV will no longer be responsible for such information. You will be responsible for communicating with such third party your desires for use of your information, including your intention to opt-out of or be removed from their distribution lists.   
  
* * *  
  
**Certain Exceptions to Non-Disclosure**

AsSeenOnTV only discloses your personal information with other companies or individuals outside of AsSeenOnTV in the following circumstances: (A) in accordance with this Privacy Policy, (B) to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies and trusted business partners or individuals for the purpose of processing personal information on our behalf, and (C) if necessary to protect our legal rights, if the information relates to actual or threatened harmful conduct, or AsSeenOnTV has good faith belief that such action is necessary to (1) conform to the requirements of law, rule, regulation or comply with governmental orders, court orders, or legal process served on AsSeenOnTV, (2) to enforce any applicable provisions of the AsSeenOnTV Terms of Use, (3) detect, prevent, assess and otherwise address fraud, security other technical issues (This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk protection), or (4) to protect and defend the property or rights of AsSeenOnTV�s Web Sites, the users of its websites or the public.

If AsSeenOnTV is ever involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, , we may sell the information you provide to us on the AsSeenOnTV websites to a third party or share your personal information with the company we merge with.   
  
* * *  
  
**How do we protect information we collect and maintain?**

We offer secure web pages to collect certain kinds of User information and we store certain kinds of data in encrypted form. We follow reasonable technical and management practices to help protect the confidentiality, security and integrity of data stored on our system. These measures include internal reviews of our collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal information. The AsSeenOnTV website servers use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), an encryption technology that works with Netscape Navigator, Microsoft Internet Explorer, Firefox, Safari, and AOL's browser, so that only AsSeenOnTV can read a customer's personal information in the possession of AsSeenOnTV.   
  
* * *  
  
**How long do we keep User information?**

We generally keep User Data on our server or in our archives for as long as we reasonably need it. We may alter this practice according to changing requirements. For example, we may delete some data if needed to free up storage space. We may keep other data for longer periods if the law requires it. In addition, information posted in a public forum could stay in the public domain indefinitely. Data management requests are administered in an orderly manner to the extent feasible and within our direct control. We have greater control over recently collected data than for archived data. Once data is removed from the system and archived, it may not be feasible to accommodate specific requests. In those cases, our general data retention policy applies.   
  
* * *  
  
**Your consent to this Privacy Policy**

By using the AsSeenONTV websites, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, as amended from time to time. The AsSeenOnTV Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy set forth the entire understanding and agreement between us with respect to the subject matter hereof. Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. Regardless, changes will be posted on the AsSeenOnTV websites which is your responsibility to review frequently. In the event of any inconsistency in the terms of this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use the provisions of the Terms of Use will take precedence over any conflicting provision in this Privacy Policy  
  
**More about our Privacy Policy**

If you have any additional questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please contact a representative at AsSeenOnTV any time through its website or at the contact numbers below.

AsSeenOnTV.com  
866-277-3366  
585-295-8600 tel.  
585-388-4390 fax  
  
<<Back
